liveukulele.com 2019-02-22

# Privacy Policy – Live Ukulele

Except as disclosed in these Terms, Live ‘Ukulele does not sell or disclose any personally identifiable information it collects about its users nor does it make it possible for third parties to contact its users directly.

 **Personal Information:** Live ‘Ukulele collects and maintains a list of email addresses. Live ‘Ukulele collects this information on a voluntary basis in order to provide its users with automatic updates of its content, and this information is not sold to or shared with other parties other than third-party services, such as Google Feedburner, which it uses to manage its subscription services. To unsubscribe, subscribers can click on the link in the email updates or adjust their subscription services at third-party websites, such as Twitter or Facebook. When posting comments on Live ‘Ukulele, the site prompts users to enter a user name, email address, and optional website; the email address is not made public on the website and is used for verification purposes only. Live ‘Ukulele reserves the right to disclose any and all personal information it collects both as required by law and when that disclosure is necessary to protect or defend its rights, property or users and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on Live ‘Ukulele.

 **Public Website:** Live ‘Ukulele is a public website. Any information users post in its comments section or any other part of the website can and will be publicly available, unless otherwise specified in these Terms. Live ‘Ukulele is not responsible for any information, personal or otherwise, users choose to submit on its website and/or any third-party contacts that result thereof.

 **Children:** Live ‘Ukulele does not intentionally gather personal information about users who are under the age of 13.

 **Anonymous Information:** Live ‘Ukulele collects non-personally identifying, aggregate information about its users, such as search engine keywords, referring/edit pages, pages visited, geographic region, operating system, browser information, date/time stamp, and hyperlinks clicked. Live ‘Ukulele uses this information for a variety of purposes, such as analyzing trends, evaluating its marketing strategies, and modifying its content. The aggregate information may be shared with and/or sold to third parties in a non-identifiable way.

 **IP Addresses:** Live ‘Ukulele automatically logs each user’s IP address with each visit and use of the website. The IP address may be linked with personally identifiable information. Unless otherwise noted in these Terms or as required by law, this information is not sold to or shared with third parties. The IP address may be used to block banned users from accessing Live ‘Ukulele.

 **Advertising:** Live ‘Ukulele uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit its website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

 **Cookies:** Live ‘Ukulele, its subscription management services, and/or its advertisers may use cookies to track users’ use of Live ‘Ukulele to improve their navigation experience. If desired, users can adjust their web browser settings to block and/or remove cookies from the computer. Live ‘Ukulele does not use cookies to track users browsing other websites. Live ‘Ukulele is not responsible for any cookies used by advertisers and/or email subscription services, and it has no knowledge of how the information gathered by the cookies can or will be used.

 **Links to Other Sites:** Live ‘Ukulele contains links to other websites, which are neither owned nor controlled by Live ‘Ukulele. When users click on a link that takes them to any other website, they have left the Live ‘Ukulele website. Live ‘Ukulele is not responsible for the privacy policies of other sites.

 **Live ‘Ukulele Content:** Live ‘Ukulele’s owners can and will post lessons, songs, reviews, interviews, and info about the ‘ukulele. All posts’ authors retain copyright to his/her respective posts on Live ‘Ukulele.

 **Affiliates:** Live ‘Ukulele is owned by Brad Bordessa. Live ‘Ukulele does not currently have any subsidiaries, joint ventures, parent company, or similar affiliates. Should another company acquire Live ‘Ukulele and/or its assets, it will own any information collected as outlined in these terms, and it will assume all rights and obligations regarding the protection and use of that information. Live ‘Ukulele will inform subscribers of any change of ownership through its subscription services.

 **Security:** Live ‘Ukulele relies on industry-standard security technologies and procedures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, disclosure, alteration, and/or destruction. Live ‘Ukulele cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with the personal information it collects, and a breech may occur.

 **Jurisdiction:** Live ‘Ukulele is based in Honoka’a, HI. As such, any information collected by Live ‘Ukulele and/or voluntarily provided by Live ‘Ukulele users will be subject to the laws and regulations of the United States. Should a dispute arise, Live ‘Ukulele users agree that any civil action or legal proceeding shall be brought in the local, state, and federal courts of record located closest to Honoka’a, HI or resolved under the rules of the American Arbitration Association ( www.adr.org).

 **Terms Updates:** The Live ‘Ukulele Terms may be changed at any time and without notice. Should Live ‘Ukulele undergo a change of ownership or make a substantial change regarding its use of personal information, Live ‘Ukulele will notify individual subscribers any subscription management services in place. Continued use of Live ‘Ukulele’s subscription services and/or accessing its site indicates your acknowledgment of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

If you have any questions or concerns about Live ‘Ukulele’s Terms of Use and Privacy Statement, email: liveukulele[at]gmail.com.
